<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Covid-19</title>
    <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid</link>
    <atom:link href="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/reports.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <description>Temporal variation in transmission during the COVID-19 outbreak
</description>
    <generator>Distill</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Global summary</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Global summary</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/global/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for the United Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in the United Kingdom. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-kingdom/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="7200" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Germany</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/germany</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Germany. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/germany</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/germany/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Brazil</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/brazil</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Brazil These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/brazil</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/brazil/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Italy</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/italy</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Italy. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/italy</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/italy/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="4800" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Russia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Russia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Europe</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/russia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="6400"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Afghanistan</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Afghanistan. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/afghanistan/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="6400"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for the United States of America</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in the United States of America. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/united-states/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="4800"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for Colombia</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in Colombia. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Americas</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/colombia/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="6400"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National and Subnational estimates for India</title>
      <link>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/india</link>
      <description>Identifying changes in the reproduction number, rate of spread, and doubling time during the course of the COVID-19 outbreak whilst accounting for potential biases due to delays in case reporting both nationally and subnationally in India. These results are impacted by changes in testing effort, increases and decreases in testing effort will increase and decrease reproduction number estimates respectively (see Methods or our [paper](https://wellcomeopenresearch.org/articles/5-112/) for further explanation).</description>
      <category>Subnational estimates</category>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <guid>https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/india</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://epiforecasts.io/covid/posts/national/india/distill-preview.png" medium="image" type="image/png" width="9600" height="4800"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
